<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Terveyssovellusryhmä8</string>
    <!--Joonaksen stringit-->
    <!--päiväkirja stringit-->
    <string name="button_teelisays"> Make an Addition! </string>
     <string name="button_avaapaivakirja"> Open Diary </string>
     <string name="textview_title"> NUTRITION DIARY </string>
     <string name="textview_paivakirjatitle"> Your Diary </string>
     <string name="button_teelisayspaivakirjassa"> Button that takes you to the page </string>
     <string name="edittext_paivamaara"> Enter Date </string>
     <string name="button_lisaa"> Update Add! </string>
     <string name="multilineedittext_kirjaus2"> Enter Here </string>
     <string name="edittext_kalorit">" Enter calories "</string>
     <string name="button_koti"> The button that takes you home </string>
     <string name="kirjotatahan"> Type here </string>
     <string name="mieliala"> mood </string>
     <string name="button_takaisin"> A button that takes you back to the diary </string>
    <string name="alertViesti">You have to enter a date before continuing</string>
    <string name="alertKyllä">Yes</string>
    <string name="alertVaroitus">Warning!</string>
    <string name="alertPoistoViesti">Do you want to delete the entry?</string>
    <string name="alertEi">No</string>
    <string name="alertOk">Okay</string>
    <string name="päivä">Day:</string>
    <string name="logi">Log:</string>
    <string name="kalorit">Calories:</string>
    <string name="mielialaString">Mood:</string>
    <string name="tyhjä">Empty</string>
    <string name="buttonTallenna">Save</string>
    <string name="buttonMuokkaa">Edit</string>
    <string name="buttonTakaisin">A button that takes you back to the last activity</string>
    <!--päiväkirja stringit loppuu-->
    <!--Joonaksen stringit loppuu-->
    <!--Tor-Erikin stringit-->
    <string name="mood1">1. How is your mood?</string>
    <string name="mood1_1">My mood is bright and good</string>
    <string name="mood1_2">I\'m not sad nor gloomy</string>
    <string name="mood1_3">I feel sad and gloomy</string>
    <string name="mood1_4">I\'m constantly low spirited and I can\'t escape it</string>
    <string name="mood1_5">I\'m so sad and depressed that I can\'t take it anymore</string>

    <string name="mood2">2. How do you feel about the future?</string>
    <string name="mood2_1">My feel for the future is hopeful</string>
    <string name="mood2_2">I don\'t feel hopeful for the future</string>
    <string name="mood2_3">Future seems pretty depressing to me</string>
    <string name="mood2_4">I feel like there\'s nothing in the future for me</string>
    <string name="mood2_5">The future seems hopeless to me and I don\'t believe it\'s going to get better</string>

    <string name="mood3">3. How do you see your life going?</string>
    <string name="mood3_1">I\'ve succeeded in life fairly often</string>
    <string name="mood3_2">I don\'t feel like I\'ve failed in life</string>
    <string name="mood3_3">I feel like I have failed in my efforts more often than usual</string>
    <string name="mood3_4">My life so far has been a series of failures</string>
    <string name="mood3_5">I feel like I\'ve completely failed as a human being</string>

    <string name="mood4">4. How satisfied or dissatisfied do you feel?</string>
    <string name="mood4_1">I\'m quite satisfied with my life</string>
    <string name="mood4_2">I\'m not particularly satisfied with my life</string>
    <string name="mood4_3">I\'m not as satisfied with things as I used to be</string>
    <string name="mood4_4">I feel like nothing satisfies me anymore</string>
    <string name="mood4_5">I\'m completely unsatisfied with everything</string>

    <string name="mood5">5. How do you feel about yourself</string>
    <string name="mood5_1">I feel like I\'m fairly decent</string>
    <string name="mood5_2">I don\'t feel like I\'m bad and worthless</string>
    <string name="mood5_3">I do feel like I\'m bad and worthless fairly often</string>
    <string name="mood5_4">I do feel like I\'m bad and worthless almost constantly</string>
    <string name="mood5_5">I am absolutely bad and worthless</string>

    <string name="mood6">6. Do you have feelings of disappointment?</string>
    <string name="mood6_1">I am happy with myself and my performance</string>
    <string name="mood6_2">I\'m not disappointed with myself</string>
    <string name="mood6_3">I am disappointed with myself</string>
    <string name="mood6_4">I feel like I\'m disgusting</string>
    <string name="mood6_5">I hate myself</string>

    <string name="mood7">7. Do you have thoughts of harming yourself?</string>
    <string name="mood7_1">I\'ve never had thoughts of suicide</string>
    <string name="mood7_2">I don\'t think or want to hurt myself</string>
    <string name="mood7_3">I feel like it would be better if I was dead</string>
    <string name="mood7_4">I have a precise plan for my suicide</string>
    <string name="mood7_5">I would kill myself if I had a chance</string>

    <string name="mood8">8. How do you feel about meeting with strangers?</string>
    <string name="mood8_1">I like meeting and chatting with people</string>
    <string name="mood8_2">I haven\'t lost interest in other people</string>
    <string name="mood8_3">OTher people don\'t interest me as much as they used to</string>
    <string name="mood8_4">I\'ve lost almost completely all my interest and feelings towards other people</string>
    <string name="mood8_5">I\'ve lost all my interest towards other people, and I don\'t care about them at all</string>

    <string name="mood9">9. How do you feel about making decisions?</string>
    <string name="mood9_1">Deciding things is easy for me</string>
    <string name="mood9_2">I can decide things like I always have</string>
    <string name="mood9_3">My confidence has diminished and I am trying to postpone decisions</string>
    <string name="mood9_4">I have great difficulties on making decisions</string>
    <string name="mood9_5">I can\'t decide anymore</string>

    <string name="mood10">10. What do you think of your being and appearance</string>
    <string name="mood10_1">I\'m fairly satisfied with my appearance</string>
    <string name="mood10_2">There\'s nothing wrong with my appearance</string>
    <string name="mood10_3">I\'m afraid I look unpleasant</string>
    <string name="mood10_4">I think I look ugly</string>
    <string name="mood10_5">I\'m sure I look ugly and unpleasant</string>

    <string name="mood11">11. How do you sleep?</string>
    <string name="mood11_1">I have no troubles sleeping</string>
    <string name="mood11_2">I sleep as well as I\'ve used to</string>
    <string name="mood11_3">I feel more tired waking up than I used to</string>
    <string name="mood11_4">Insomnia bothers me</string>
    <string name="mood11_5">I suffer from insomnia, difficulty falling asleep, or waking up too early</string>

    <string name="mood12">12. Do you feel tired and exhausted?</string>
    <string name="mood12_1">Being tired and exhausted is almost foreign to me</string>
    <string name="mood12_2">I don\'t get more exhausted than I\'ve used to</string>
    <string name="mood12_3">I do get tired more easily than before</string>
    <string name="mood12_4">Even the minor tasks tire and exhaust me</string>
    <string name="mood12_5">I\'m too exhausted to do anything</string>

    <string name="mood13">13. How is your appetite?</string>
    <string name="mood13_1">There\'s nothing wrong with my appetite</string>
    <string name="mood13_2">My appetite is as it used to be</string>
    <string name="mood13_3">My appetite is worse than it used to</string>
    <string name="mood13_4">My appetite is a lot worse than before</string>
    <string name="mood13_5">I have absolutely no appetite</string>

    <string name="mood14">14. Are you anxious and tense?</string>
    <string name="mood14_1">I consider myself quite nervous and I don’t get anxious very easily</string>
    <string name="mood14_2">I don\'t feel anxious or "nervous"</string>
    <string name="mood14_3">I get anxious and nervous easily</string>
    <string name="mood14_4">I become particularly painful, anxious, or tense</string>
    <string name="mood14_5">I feel constantly anxious and painful as if my nerves are "exhausted"</string>

    <string name="depression1">No symptoms of depression</string>
    <string name="depression2">Mild depressive symptoms</string>
    <string name="depression3">Moderate depressive symptoms</string>
    <string name="depression4">Serious depressive symptoms</string>

    <string name="forwards">Next</string>
    <string name="backwards">Previous</string>
    <string name="end">Results</string>
    <!--Tor-Erikin stringit loppuu-->
    <!--Aleksin stringit alkaa-->

    <!--Aloitus Stringit alkaa-->
    <string name="oletustextview"> default text </string>
    <string name="textViewAloitusEka"> Welcome </string>
    <string name="textViewAloitusToka"> Use Diary for the first time </string>
    <string name="textViewAloitusVanha"> Welcome back </string>
    <string name="textViewAloitusVanha2"> To use the Diary application </string>
    <!--Aloitus Stringit Loppuu-->
    <!--Esittää Stringit alkaa-->
    <string name = "Lainausteksti1"> When you replace negative thoughts with positive ones, you start with positive results. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti2"> A small positive change can change your entire day or your entire life. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti3"> Good things happen every day. We just have to tell you about them. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti4"> You can only change yourself, but sometimes it changes everything. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti5"> We awaken in others with the same mental attitude we have towards them. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti6"> A negative situation is always converted to a positive one. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti7"> We are what we think. Everything we are comes from our thoughts. We\'re thinking of building the world. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti8"> We can change our lives. We can do, be and be exactly what we want. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti9"> Everything is a seed. If you’re sitting on rotten seeds, don’t rely on picking delicious apples. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti10"> Everything is either a growth opportunity or a barrier to growth. You can decide. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti11"> A positive attitude can really make me dream, he did it for me. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti12"> A pessimist sees difficulties at every opportunity. The optimist sees the opportunity in any difficulty. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti13"> What you become is more important than what you get. What you get affects what you are. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti14"> Learn how to be happy with what you have when you continue what you want. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti15"> Happiness is not procrastination. Thats something youre planning for now. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti16"> The greatest value in life is not what you get. The greatest value in life is what you become. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti17"> You can\'t have a positive life and a negative mind. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti18"> Nothing can scare you if you refuse to be afraid. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti19"> The only place where your dreams are impossible is in your mind. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti20">Learning is a gift. Even if the pain is your teacher. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti21"> Love the life you have to live in the life you love. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti22"> Your smile gives you a positive look that makes you feel better. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti23"> The person who can bring laughter to the room is blessed. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti24"> When you are excited about what you are doing, feel the positive energy. It is very simple. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti25"> When a person really wants something, the whole universe secretly helps them realize their dreams. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti26"> Winners tend to create their own expectations before the event. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti27"> Man is nothing but the product of his thought. That will be what he thinks. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti28"> You\'re never too old to have another goal or another dream. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti29"> Worst times can be best if you think positive energy. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti30"> Keep your face facing the sun and you won\'t see a single shadow. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti31"> You are capable of much more than you think, imagine or do now. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti32"> Live life to the fullest and focus on the positive. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti33"> The world is what we think. If we can change our thoughts, we can change the world. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti34"> Many times people see the downside of what they can\'t do. I always look at what I can do. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti35"> Constant optimism is a factor in power. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti36"> We are all here for a special reason. Stop being a prisoner of the past. Become the architect of the future. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti37"> The only difference between a good and a bad day is attitude. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti38"> The only thing that stands out in a person and what he wants in life is often a willingness to try and believe that it is possible to achieve it. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti39"> Taking the right attitude can turn negative stress into positive ones. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti40"> Nevertheless, I think people are good at heart. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti41"> A strong and positive self-image is the best way to prepare for success. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti42">The sun does not shine on a few flowers and trees, but on the joy of the whole world. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti43"> Find a place in your interior where joy burns. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti44"> You need to start thinking the way you want to. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti45"> A very positive attitude creates more miracles than any medicine. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti46"> Pessimism leads to weakness, to the power of optimism. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti47"> The situation is not bad, your thoughts on the situation are negative. Change them. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti48"> The only disability in life is bad attitude. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti49"> In order to take positive action, we need to develop a positive vision. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti50"> Say and do something positive that will improve the situation; it doesn\'t take the brain to complain. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti51"> If you don\'t make mistakes, you won\'t do anything. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti52"> To succeed, you need to find something to catch, something to motivate you, something to inspire you. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti53"> These are my latest words for you. Don\'t be afraid of life. Believe it is worth living and your faith will create a fact. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti54"> A little positive thought in the morning can change your whole day. </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija54" >Author unknown</string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti55"> Our minds can change what matters because we live up to our expectations. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti56"> Im optimistic. There is no point in being anything else. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti57"> Once in the valley, keep that goal in mind and have new energy to continue climbing. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti58"> Feed your mind as if you were in your body. The mind can\'t cope with junk. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti59">This is the law of attraction: you don\'t get what you want. You can attract what you are. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti60"> Write in your heart that every day is the best day of the year. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti61"> The attitude of positive expectations is a sign of a higher personality. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti62"> A positive thinker sees the impossible, feels the intangible, and achieves the impossible. </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija62"> Author unknown </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti63"> Don\'t let the negativity of the world stop you. Instead, give yourself what motivates you. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti64"> It\'s a lousy habit; Happy is the habit; and the choice is yours. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti65"> Work hard, be positive, and get up early. That\'s the best part of the day. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti66"> Optimism is the most important human trait, as it allows us to improve our situation and hope for a better tomorrow. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti67"> Refuse to comment on your attitude. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti68"> The world is moving so fast these days that a man who says you can\'t do something is interrupted by someone who does it. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti69"> If someone says you can\'t, it really means I can\´t. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti70"> There are two ways to light: be a candle or a mirror that reflects it. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti71"> While frustration is sometimes painful, it is a very positive and essential part of success. </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija71"> Author unknown </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti72"> Be honest with you and have positive people around you. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti73"> Positive thinking allows you to do something better than negative thinking. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti74"> If you don\'t protect something, nothing fell. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti75"> Love yourself. It\'s important to stay positive because beauty is coming out. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti76"> A person is great because he or she has great qualities, not because there are no flaws. </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija76"> Author unknown </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti77"> Don\'t let people respect you. Surround yourself with positive people. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti78"> The past has no power at this time. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti79"> When I do good, I feel good. When I do evil, I feel evil. This is my religion. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti80"> The best way to gain self-esteem is to do what we fear. </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija80" > Author unknown </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti81"> We have the ability to decide which thoughts to stop at. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti82"> A mediocre idea that excites goes beyond a great idea that doesn\'t inspire anyone. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti83"> It\'s great to be optimistic. Keeps you healthy and flexible. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti84"> It\'s amazing If you leave it, life will change in a positive way quickly. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti85"> When you encounter a negative situation, don\'t think about it. Make it positive. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti86"> Work on energy and peace, knowing that the right thoughts and efforts will inevitably produce the right results. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti87"> I may not have gotten where I was trying to go, but I think I\'m ready where I needed to be. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti88"> Every day brings new opportunities. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti89"> Repeated playback leads to conviction. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti90"> Anger has caused many problems in this world and has not solved it. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti91"> A person is the product of their dreams. So make sure you dream big dreams. And then try to live your dream. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti92"> If you don\'t like something, change it. If you can\'t change it, change your attitude. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti93"> We rejoice in the beauty of the butterfly, but rarely acknowledge the changes that have taken place to achieve that beauty. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti94"> I\'d rather die chasing what I want, living what I\'m doing. </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija94"> Author unknown </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti95"> We invite good luck with good attitude, effort, risk, continuity and show. </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija95"> Author unknown </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti96"> The most important type of freedom is what you really are. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti97"> If you find a path without obstacles, it will probably lead to nothing. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti98"> This is not a goal. It\'s about becoming a person who can accomplish this goal. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti99"> End the day with a positive thought. Tomorrow you have the opportunity to do better </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija99"> Author unknown </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti100"> If the opportunity doesn\'t ring, build a door. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti101"> If we grow up, we\'re always out of our comfort zone. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti102"> Hope is a dream of a resurrected man. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti103"> Be grateful for what you have; you end up getting more. If you focus on what you don’t have, you’ll never have enough </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija103"> Author unknown </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti104"> I\'m a positive thinker, and I think that helps me in the hardest times. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti105"> I don\'t know, man, I need to know him better. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti106"> Without humble but reasonable confidence in your own strength, you cannot be successful or happy. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti107"> Inspiration comes from you. Must be positive. When you are, good things happen. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti108"> The best thing you can give your enemies is forgiveness; to the opponent, tolerance; to a friend, to your heart; good child, good example; father, respect; to your mother, be proud; to yourself, love you; for everyone, for charity. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti109"> Next time you feel a little uncomfortable with the pressure of your life, remember that without pressure, there are no diamonds. Pressure is part of success. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti110"> How great it is that no one has to wait a moment to heal the world. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti111"> Compassion, love, happiness, we all have these qualities, but we don\'t usually use them. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti112"> I don\'t want to live in vain like most people do. I want to be helpful or bring joy to people, even those I have never met. I want to continue living after death. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti113"> You can\'t set any restrictions. The more you dream, the farther you get. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti114"> Think first about what you really want. Then persecute him stubbornly, do not give up. When you fall, think about the rewards. You\'ve reached 50% of your goal. </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija114"> Author unknown </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti115"> Attitude is everything; It covers what we do, what we say, what we think, and what we get. </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija115"> Author unknown </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti116"> The best is yet to come, as long as you want </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija116"> Author unknown </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti117"> Positive thoughts don\'t automatically get impossible things, but impossible things can\'t be achieved without positive thoughts </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija117"> Author unknown </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti118"> The secret to success is to learn to use pain and pleasure instead of pain and joy. If you do, you will be in control of your life. If not, life will guide you </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija118"> Author unknown </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti119"> We don\'t see things as they are, we see them as we are. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti120"> Happiness, like an accident, is a proactive choice. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti121"> You can\'t make positive choices in your life without an environment that makes them simple, natural, and enjoyable choices. </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija121"> Author unknown </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti122"> A positive attitude causes a chain reaction of thoughts, events, and positive results. It is a catalyst and produces exceptional results. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti123"> There is virtually nothing impossible in this world if you simply put your mind to it and maintain a positive attitude. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti124"> The time you enjoy wasting was not wasted. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti125"> Never say anything about yourself that you don\'t want to become a reality. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti126"> Be bold Take risks Nothing can replace experience. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti127"> The more aware we are of what we really are, the less trouble we will have. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti128"> You can\'t stop the waves, but you can learn to surf. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti129"> Think of what you need, think of what others need. </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija129"> Author unknown </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti130"> There are always flowers for those who want to see them. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti131"> Always end the day with a positive thought. No matter how hard things were, there is a good opportunity tomorrow to make them better </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija131"> Author unknown </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti132"> People become truly exceptional when they start thinking they can do things. When they believe in themselves, they have the first secret to success. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti133"> Learn to smile in all situations. See it as an opportunity to test your strengths and abilities. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti134"> The day is what you make of him. Why not have a good day ?. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti135"> We are responsible for who we are, and no matter what we want to be, we have the power to make ourselves. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti136"> You have done this before and you can do it now. Look at the positive possibilities. Direct the significant energy of your frustration and turn it into a positive, effective, and unstoppable definition. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti137"> A positive attitude is that everyone can work and learn to use it. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti138"> Remember your dreams and fight for them. You need to know what you want out of life. There is only one thing that makes your dream impossible: the fear of failure. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti139"> How can I live today tomorrow I\'m committed ?. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti140"> I believe anything is possible if you have the mentality, the will and the desire to do it and dedicate your time. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti141"> There is a small difference between people, but this difference is a big difference. The small difference is the attitude. The big difference is whether it\'s positive or negative. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti142"> Positive thinking is more than a slogan. It changes the way we behave. I firmly believe that when I am positive, I am better and others are better. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti143"> It\'s during our darkest moments when we need to focus on looking at the light. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti144"> After all, we don\'t remember the words of our enemies, but the silence of our friends. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti145"> We have to accept a limited disappointment, but we never lose infinite hope. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti146"> You have to accept what\'s coming, and the only important thing is that you face it with courage and in the best possible way. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti147"> You must first learn the rules of the game. Then you have to play better than anyone. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti148"> Correction does a lot, but the mood does a lot more. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti149"> It is not about the situation, it is about whether we react negatively or positively. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti150"> The difference between winning and losing often doesn\'t give up. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti151"> A positive attitude may not solve all problems, but it does distract enough people. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti152"> If you\'re not excited, you\'ll be eagerly ignited. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti153"> Concern often overshadows something small. </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija153"> Swiss proverb </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti154"> The best preparation for tomorrow is to give you the best today. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti155"> Put your heart, mind, and soul into even the smallest deeds. That\'s the secret to success. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti156"> Optimism is a belief that guides achievement. Nade is possible without hope and trust. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti157"> If you can dream it, you can do it. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti158"> Keep your eyes on the stars and your feet on the ground. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti159"> Remember: a book, a pen, a child, and a teacher can change the world. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti160"> All you need is a plan, a roadmap, and the courage to go. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti162"> Keep your dreams alive. Understand that faith in yourself, vision, hard work, determination, and dedication is needed to accomplish everything. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti163"> Faith is a bird that feels light when dawn is still dark. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti164"> Take a positive attitude every day, trying to be better. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti165"> Don\'t let yesterday take a lot today. </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija165"> Author unknown </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti166"> Learn more about failure than success. Don\'t let it stop you. Failure to build character. </string>
    <string name = "Lainaustekija166"> Author unknown </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti167"> Stay positive and happy. Work hard and don’t lose hope. Stay open to criticism and keep learning. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti168"> Positive action combined with positive thoughts is a success. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti169"> Successful people have a positive outlook on life no matter what happens around them. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti170"> Every day is 1440 minutes. This means we have 1,440 positive opportunities every day. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti171"> If you have a positive attitude and are constantly striving to do your best, you can eventually overcome immediate problems and find yourself ready for bigger challenges. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti172"> Attitude is like a sign that gives color to your world. Color the gray image constantly, and the image is always gloomy. Try adding colors to your images, including your mood, and they\'ll work out. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti173"> Few things in the world are stronger than a positive impulse. Smile A world of optimism and hope. You can do it. when things get tough. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti174"> Good laughter is the sun in the house. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti175"> The key is to inspire people to be great at what they want to do. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti176"> No matter what you\'re going through, there\'s a light at the end of the tunnel, and it may seem hard to reach, but you can find the positive side if you keep working. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti177"> Trust dreams because they hide eternity forever. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti178"> The ability to stay calm and focused on stressful situations is critical to making positive decisions. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti179"> You need to be able to deal with stress because hard times are coming and a positive outlook is what you can overcome. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti180"> Every day you wake up, you have two options. You can be positive or negative; optimistic or pessimistic. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti181"> You can do anything to prevent bad things from happening to you, but in the end something bad will happen, so the best prevention is a positive attitude. </string>
    <string name = "Lainausteksti182"> If you choose, even unexpected setbacks can bring new and positive opportunities. </string>
    <string name="Lainaustekija47">Author unknown</string>

    <string name="Lainausteksti161">" Start where you are, use what you have. Do what you can. "</string>

</resources>